Looks like it'll be pretty late by the time we get back.
Sorry about that, Grete.
Please, don't apologize.
If anything, I should be thanking you for
spending the whole day with me.
Thea and the others should be back
from the mission site by now.
Everyone's probably waiting for us.
This will be the first time in a long while
that we'll have all nine Lamplight
members back together.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Um, boss?
Would it be all right if we made one more stop?
I want to get something for the team.
Closed?
Oh no...
Was it all for nothing?
All that work we did?
Several Weeks Ago, After the First Mission
FILE: Daughter Dearest Grete
For the next  little while,
I'm going to be staying in the Lylat Kingdom.
Don't do anything too wild,
and make sure you all get plenty of rest.
Yes, sir!
He's gone...
Woohoo!
It's vacation time!
We have ten whole days off!
Hey, we've earned it.
I'm heading out tomorrow to travel my heart out!
I'm gonna go on an adventure with Erna and Sara, yo.
Nobody told me Annette was
going to be tagging along!
Don't be like that.
It'll be more fun with all three of us.
All right, everyone, listen up!
We're all free to spend our vacations however we want,
but tonight, we should all have a feast together.
With no Teach and no training, the night is ours!
Yay!
I can't hear you!
Is that really all the excitement you've got?
YAY!
I can't wait!
In that case, what do you say to having
one of those meat pies as our main dish?
Meat pie...
You mean, like the one you got while you were
out on that errand the other day?
That's the one!
That was tasty as heck!
I was blown away, yo!
Yeah, me too.
Me three.
Me four.
No objections here!
Let's head over to the shop, then.
While we're out, we can pick up some other food, too.
Looks like it's closed.
Oh, I remember you.
Are these your friends from seminary school?
That's right.
May I ask why you aren't open?
Actually, I'm thinking about closing up shop for good.
Smells like raw garbage.
Did someone dump something here?
Y-you can tell?
If it's not a bother,
would you mind telling us what happened?
I mean, you ask, but...
It would mean a lot to me.
The other day, the president of Mannheim Inc.
came here in person.
Mannheim?
The food company?
Like, the one with the radio jingle?
"Ma-Ma-Mannheim's, Fried-Fried Chicken!
Ma-Ma-Mannheim's, Fried-Fri-"
He wanted me to sell him my meat pie recipe.
But he only offered me a pittance,
and it came with the absurd requirement that
I never sell meat pies from this shop again.
And when you turned him down,
the harassment started.
Makes sense.
I'm no spring chicken anymore.
And I don't have anyone to take over the shop,
so I was thinking that maybe I should
just call it quits and sell the recipe.
This shop has been a beloved
local institution for ages.
There are hundreds if not thousands of people
who love your pies,
and we all count ourselves among them.
That's because this place has been
passed down for generations.
But sometimes, that's just the way things go.
Those kind words of yours are enough for me, miss.
That totally killed the mood, yo.
Yeep.
It sucks, but them's the breaks.
What say we find something else for our main dish?
No, we can't...
What would the boss do if he were in this situation?
What does Klaus have to do with anything?
It's nothing.
All righty.
Ayup.
Time to crush Mannheim.
Mannheim's gotta go.
Lily, Sybilla...
Let's all just hold on a minute.
I understand how you feel,
but what exactly do you intend on doing?
Poison their president.
Beat up their president.
That's so crude!
You know that's a civilian you're talking about, right?
Hey, Mannheim Inc.'s the one committin' the crimes.
We have no proof of that.
This is a major corporation we're talking about.
Its president will have wealth and power in spades,
and I strongly doubt that he's doing
any of the harassment himself.
Look, I'm angry too.
But punishing the president won't do anything
to repair the damage he's caused.
From the sound of it, the owner's lost
his motivation to keep running the shop.
I disagree.
This is a problem that we have the power to solve.
You've got a plan, Grete?
I do.
However, it's going to require
everybody's help to pull off.
So it's decided.
Let's get started, then.
Just for the record,
Klaus told us not to do anything too wild.
Let's do this!
Down with Mannheim!
Yeah!
When their director of general affairs came to the club,
he told me that Mannheim Inc.
just had a new president take over.
I see.
Itami ga unda daishou
Embrace the toll of pain
The new guy is an imbecile.
He trashed their earnings in record time,
Nido to kienai kasabuta wo dakishime
The scabs that will never fade
and everyone in the company hates him.
Gouin na sukimakaze ano hi sarawareta
That day, a forceful draft snatched it away
Kawarenai boku wa oiteikanakucha
Unable to change, I have to leave it behind
He's worried about keeping his position,
so he wants something that can
Nee fuan sae oikoshite
Come, outrace your fear
turn the situation around all at once.
That's probably why he's after the recipe, yeah?
Shiranakatta sora to kyou wa kono ashi de
Face the unfamiliar sky and day on your own two feet
Chouyou wo mukaeyou
And greet the sunrise
Fukou ga kureta shiawase
Misfortune gave rise to happiness
I posed as her and tried snoopin' around their clients.
Zetsubou no hate ni mieta
You saw a guidepost at the end of despair
Looks like the second-gen idiot
Shirube wa ima hitosuji no hi wo tomosu
And now, it's lit with a single flame
made some seedy friends as a kid.
Karamiau kako wo harae
Shake off the entangled past
They're probably the ones behind the harassment.
Kokoro ga hokorobu basho made aragau
And fight until you find a place your heart can soar
Do they have connections to organized crime?
Probably.
And there are rumors
that the new president secretly carries a gun around.
Ah, shunkan ikinobiro
Ah, surviving through each moment
That's why no one can stand up to him.
We'll need to make sure this doesn't get out of hand.
Thanks to everyone's hard work,
we've gathered the intel we need.
Now, I have a question.
Out of all of us, who would you say
looks the most gullible?
Lily.
Excuse me?!
Then it's unanimous.
Now, please commit this document to memory.
Lily, would you mind giving me a
final check on that backstory?
You got it!
I'm Lily, or rather Lillian,
the granddaughter of the meat pie shop owner
who oh so loves the pies her granddad made.
He even taught me his recipe
so I could take over the shop someday.
But alas!
Lillian could never give up on her dream
of becoming an actress!
To pie, or to act?
After agonizing over it for ages, she left home.
Now, she struggles alone in a run-down
apartment near the capital,
working her butt off day in and day out.
However, her acting career never took off,
and she lives her life in poverty.
Oh-oh-oh, poor Lillian,
your tale brings a tear to my eye.
Thank you.
That was perfect.
That's him! The target's here!
Th-the president of Mannheim Inc.?
But what brings you here?
Your adorable little blonde friend
told me your address.
I hear you're a little hard up for cash, Miss Lillian.
Your grandfather taught you
the meat pie recipe, did he not?
My company would love to buy it from you.
S-so, about that...
There's actually someone else
who wants to buy grandpa's recipe, too.
I see.
Someone beat me to the punch, did they?
Please, sell it to us anyways!
I'll pay you a thousand dents.
That'll cover your rent here for three months.
For real?!
You're up, Sis!
Very well.
I'm code name Daughter Dearest.
Now, let's fill this time with laughter and tears.
Plus, if you're willing to become my lover,
then I'll throw in another two hundred dents a month.
I'll sock you, y'know.
Sorry, what was that?
Ah, there they are!
It's the other pair that wanted to buy the recipe!
Oh dear!
You have another visitor, Lillian?
Yeah, sorry.
You look familiar...
It can't be!
Yup!
Allow me to introduce you.
This here is the world-famous chef
known as the pride of the Lylat Kingdom...
...Sean Dumont!
FILE: Daughter Dearest Grete
All in all, there were four traps we set.
The first was information.
Thea used the Mannheim director of generals affairs
to let the president know that Lillian existed.
The second was the photo.
Monika's talent for forgery allowed us
to lend credence to our story.
The third was Erna.
She has a tendency to attract
villains and accidents to her.
By taking advantage of that,
we were able to use the president's unsavory friends
to indirectly let him know the apartment's address
as well as the fact that Lillian was financially struggling.
And now, the fourth.
What?! B-but that's impossible!
Sean Dumont is one of the best chefs in the world!
There's no way a legend like him would
take an interest in a tiny rural nation like ours!
But it's true, though.
A mere thousand dents for that meat pie recipe?
It's sad that a food company's president
would be so inept at judging value.
Wh-
Mr. Dumont is prepared to offer you 200,000 dents.
T-two hundred thousand?!
All you have to do is say yes, Miss Lillian,
and we'll have the paperwork drawn up right away.
Furthermore, our restaurant is frequented by
famous actors from around the world.
We would be happy to introduce you to some of them.
Sold!
Then we have a deal.
You people think you can just march in here
and do whatever the hell you want?!
Hold on! That recipe is-
If you want to go up against us, then be my guest.
Just be warned that all Mr. Dumont has to do
is say that Mannheim's food tastes bad,
and your company will crumble in the blink of an eye.
The meat pie recipe is ours now.
From now on, make sure you stay away from
Miss Lillian and her grandfather.
Yay! Stage one, complete!
All we have to do now is wait for Mannheim's
president to get in touch with Lillian again.
I rigged up a dummy line so the president's call
will come straight here, yo.
How about that awesome performance I put on, huh?
I thought my acting was quite good as well.
Yeah, yeah.
Things couldn't have gone better.
What do you think, Erna?
You're too close.
Get away from me.
Good work today.
Things always seem to go smoothly
when you're the one running the show.
That's very nice of you to say.
You sure you aren't pushing yourself, though?
I wasn't expecting you to put so much into this.
The truth is, I visited that pie shop with the boss once.
Yeah, that figures.
You want to tell me about it?
Oh, right.
If you ever get a chance,
you should check out that shop.
Huh?
The meat pies there are the best I've ever had.
They're so tasty I actually tried to recreate them once,
but I wasn't able to pull it off.
Not even with your skills?
Nope.
I was able to make something exceedingly close,
but it wasn't quite the same as the real deal.
The generations of love they've passed down
aren't the kind of thing you can
reproduce in a single day.
Love, passed down...
In other words, you're saying that you want me
to receive the love you're passing along?
I am not.
That sounded like a proposal to me.
See, now you're just ignoring my feelings altogether.
It was just a recommendation.
I have a lot of memories of going there with Inferno.
You do?
We ate there as a reward for a mission well done.
There was a man named Lukas who loved the place.
He and I always fought over the last slice,
and my mentor would end up scolding us.
I guess I'll never be able to
enjoy their pies that way again.
That's why I can't let the shop be destroyed
while the boss is away.
How noble.
You're going to quite some lengths to protect
what the person you love cares about.
Am I making a mistake, do you think?
Who knows?
But here's the thing.
You really think Klaus is going to be happy about this?
What?
Tell me, did he ever once ask you
to protect the meat pie shop?
He gave us two instructions, right?
"Don't do anything too wild," and
"make sure you get plenty of rest."
The way I see it,
you've gone and ignored both of those.
Would Klaus really want us to
use the skills he taught us
to shake down some petty lowlife?
Psych.
I was joking.
C'mon, chin up.
I'm just screwing with you.
I can't help but get jealous when I see someone
being all earnest about their love.
Monika...
That's him!
President Dumbass fell for it hook, line, and sinker!
Isn't it weird how soon he called, though?
I'm so sorry.
This wasn't what I expected.
Please hold off on signing that contract
with Sean Dumont, Miss Lillian.
What? But...
I'll give you 250,000 dents.
Please, sell the recipe to Mannheim Inc.
250,000?!
Everything up until there went as planned.
The fact that the recipe had the seal of approval
from a world-famous chef
would have made the president want it that much more.
The plan was, we would sell him a fake recipe
and give the money we got to the
meat pie shop owner, but...
However, I have one condition.
You do?
That's right.
I need you to prepare the recipe in front of me
and make a pie that's the exact same
as the ones from the shop.
So, we're boned, yeah?
We don't have any idea what the real recipe is.
Yeah.
We need to procure a genuine meat pie.
The problem is, what we're doing is fraud.
We can't let the pie shop owner
become an accomplice.
Yo, Grete, what should we do?
Give up on the cash and walk away?
Hey, Grete.
According to the story you told me,
didn't Klaus try to recreate the meat pie?
There's an international call for you, sir.
Here's the recipe.
Ingredient set A: ground shoulder roast, onion,
Annette, could you fast forward?
carrot, apple, garlic-
...suitable amounts of each.
Ingredient set B: bread flour, pastry flour,
Fast forward again.
cornstarch, water-
...suitable amounts of each.
Instructions, part one.
Mix A until it becomes the color of a single drop of blue paint
spilled into the sun as it sets over Emai Lake.
Instructions, part two.
Fast forward!
Mix B-
...part four.
Once the sear marks become bubbly-crunchy, take it out.
Bubbly-crunchiness is delicious.
That concludes the recipe.
I don't know what you need it for, but good hunting.
How the hell are we supposed to follow that?!
All the quantities were "suitable amounts."
In other words, it's the same
"somehow or other" stuff as always.
I'm all out of ideas, yo.
No, no. I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
This is my first vacation with you all,
and I think I let myself get carried away.
Perhaps the boss told us not to do anything too wild
because he thought something like this might happen.
Miss Grete...
I wanted to understand the boss's feelings and
do what I could to support them, but now...
So, you mind fixing it?
"Good hunting," huh?
Klaus probably has some idea of what's up.
This time, make sure you actually
understand what he's thinking.
Monika...
You're the only one who's got any shot
of cracking that cipher of a recipe.
You can say that again.
All righty!
Down with Mannheim!
Let's give this one more push to support Grete's love!
Yeah!
It'll be finished in just a sec.
Good.
Ahhh! A-a mouse!
Here we go.
Is something the matter?
N-no, nothing.
Mmm, delicious!
This is the shop's pie, for sure!
I'm certain this is the real recipe!
Then I guess I'll be taking this money.
I'm through with you.
If you're smart, you won't resist.
Oh no, what a bummer!
I really didn't want to have to use this.
Not against a civvie.
What are you babbling about-
Did the knockout gas work?
Like a charm.
Then it's time to withdraw.
The mission is complete.
From there, we anonymously donated the money here.
I assumed the shop would be up and running again.
All right, I'm counting on you.
Oh, it's you.
If I may, why are you closed?
Oh! If you're worried about that mess I was in,
that all sorted itself out.
But my back isn't what it used to be, you see.
Sir! I, um, baked it just like you showed me.
That's what I like to hear!
I'll be right over.
As you can see, I decided to take on an apprentice.
The shop should be open again before too long,
so I hope you can wait a bit longer.
How lovely!
The sample pie I baked will be ready soon.
Would you like to take it?
We would love to.
I did offer to carry it.
I appreciate the offer.
However, I'd like to give it to the others myself.
You really can be stubborn when it comes to the team.
It's embarrassing to admit,
but I assumed that sooner or later,
everyone on the team would develop
romantic feelings for you.
I figured that someday,
we would all end up fighting over you,
and the team would collapse from within.
Don't even say that.
That's a horrible thought.
But during the break,
everyone helped support my love for you.
Is that so?
Lamplight really is a wonderful team.
W-we've got trouble!
What's wrong?
You look alarmed.
S-so, uh, Thea and the others just stayed
behind at your mission site
to clean up a few loose ends, right?
That was the plan, why?
They aren't back yet.
I tried calling, but they didn't pick up.
What?
Judgin' by your expression,
you didn't see this coming either.
D-did something happen to them?
You're up.
So, what's it going to be?
About what?
Don't play dumb.
We're short on time.
Hurry up and make your choice.
Are you going to betray Lamplight?
If so, I'd appreciate it if you told me.
I'll need some time to dispose of your body.